picknpay.co.za 2015-05-24

# Pick n Pay Privacy Policy - Pick n Pay

This Website is an interactive online service operated by Pick n Pay Retailers (Proprietary) Limited. This Privacy Policy applies to this site (however accessed and/or used, whether via personal computers, mobile devices or otherwise, and other interactive features, applications or downloads that are operated by us that are available through this site or that interact with this site and post this Privacy Policy (collectively known as this “Website”). This Privacy Policy doesn’t apply to our collection of information from other sources, unless specifically stated.

We have adopted this Privacy Policy to explain what information may be collected on our Website, how we use this information and under what circumstances we may disclose the information to third parties. This Privacy Policy, together with the Terms of Use and Copyright Policy posted on our Website sets forth the general rules and policies governing your use of our Website. Depending on your activities when visiting our Website, you may be required to agree to additional terms and conditions.

We keep this Privacy Policy posted on our Website, and you should review it frequently as we reserve the right to change it from time to time without prior notice to you. Any changes are effective immediately on posting. We will not use your personally identifiable information without your consent in a manner materially different than what was stated at the time it was collected. WHEN YOU ACCESS OUR WEBSITE YOU AGREE TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY, OR TO ANY CHANGES WE MAY SUBSEQUENTLY MAKE, YOU MUST IMMEDIATELY STOP ACCESSING OUR WEBSITE.

**Type Of Information The Website Collects**

The Website generally collects personally identifying information with your specific knowledge and consent. For instance, when you enter any competition, complete a survey, make a purchase or register for any portion of our services, you are asked to provide information such as your e-mail address, name or phone number. Optional information such as your age and gender may also be requested.

Our servers may also automatically collect information about your computer when you visit the Website, including without limitation the type of browser software you use, the operating system you are running, the Website that referred you, and your Internet Protocol address.

**How The Information Is Used**

The personally identifying information you supply through the Website is used to provide you with the service you have requested, to respond to your inquiries or in other ways naturally associated with the circumstances in which you provided the information. For example, we may use your e-mail address to send you a confirmation notice. We may also use the information to communicate with you about new features, products or services, and/or to improve the services that we offer by tailoring them to your needs. You may opt-out from receiving future promotional information from us or our affiliated companies, or direct that we not share your information with any affiliated companies.

We also allow access to our database by third parties that provide us with services, such as technical maintenance, vendors that process credit card orders, deliver our merchandise, administer our promotions, provide us with marketing or promotional assistance, analyse our data, assist us with customer service, etc. Our vendors agree to use this information, and we share information with them, only to carry out our requests. In addition, we may share your information with participating sponsors to a programme or competition you enter via our Website, our co-promotional partners and others with whom we have marketing or other relationships. Other than as provided in this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use, or as set forth when you submit the information to the Website, we will not share or sell your personally identifiable information to third parties without your consent.

We reserve the right to use the information we collect about your computer, which may at times be able to identify you, for any lawful business purpose, including without limitation to help diagnose problems with our servers, to gather broad demographic information and to otherwise administer our Website.

While your personally identifiable information is protected as outlined above, we reserve the right to use, transfer, sell, and share aggregated, anonymous data about our users as a group for any business purpose, such as analysing usage trends and seeking compatible advertisers and partners.

In addition, as our business changes, we may buy or sell various assets. In the event all or a portion of the assets owned or controlled by Pick n Pay , its parent or any subsidiary or affiliated entity are sold, assigned, transferred or acquired by another company, the information from and/or about our Website users may be among the transferred assets.

**Cookies**

A cookie is a piece of information that is deposited on your computer’s hard drive by your web browser when you use our computer server. The cookies enable us to recognise you and give us information about your previous visits. We learn which advertisements bring users to our Website. Most browsers accept cookies automatically, but usually you can alter your settings to prevent automatic acceptance. If you choose not to accept cookies, this may disable some of the features of our Website. The information that we collect and may share with our advertisers is anonymous and not personally identifiable. It does not contain your name, address, telephone number or email address.

**Mobile Device Identifiers**

Certain mobile service providers uniquely identify mobile devices and we or our third-party service providers may receive such device information if you access the Website through mobile devices. Certain features of our Website may require collection of mobile phone numbers, and we may associate that phone number to mobile device identification information. Additionally, some mobile phone service providers operate systems that pinpoint the physical location of devices that use their service. Depending on the provider, we or our third-party service providers may receive this information.

**Embedded Scripts**

An embedded script is a programming code that is designed to collect information about your interactions with the Website, such as the links you click on. The code is temporarily downloaded onto your computer from our web server or a third-party service provider, is active only while you are connected to the Website, and is deactivated or deleted thereafter.

Information collected through passive means may be non-identifying or may be associated with you. If the latter, it will be treated as personally identifiable information.

**Information You Provide About A Third Party**

If you send someone else a communication from the Website, such as sending Website content to a friend, the information you provide (names, e-mail addresses etc.) is used to facilitate the communication and is not used for any other marketing purpose unless we obtain consent from that person or we explicitly say otherwise. Please be aware that when you use any send-to-a-friend functionality on our Website, your e-mail address may be included in the communication sent to your friend.

**Information Provided By Third Parties About You**

From time to time, we may supplement the information we collect with outside records from third parties in order to enhance our ability to serve you, to tailor our content to you and to offer you opportunities to purchase products or services that we believe may be of interest to you. We may combine the information we receive from those other sources with the information we collect through the Website. In those cases, we will apply this Privacy Policy to any personal identifiable information received, unless otherwise specifically disclosed by us at the time you provide your personally identifiable information.

**Information Security And Notification**

Because no data transmission over the internet is completely secure, and no system of physical or electronic security is impenetrable, Pick n Pay cannot guarantee the security of the information you send to us or the security of our servers or databases, and by using the Website you agree to assume all risk in connection with the information sent to us or collected by us when you use the Website. In the unlikely event that we believe that the security of your information in our possession or control may have been compromised, we may seek to notify you. If notification is appropriate, we may notify you by e-mail, provided that we have your e-mail address.

Notwithstanding anything to the contrary in this Privacy Policy, we reserve the right to disclose any personally identifiable or non-personal information about you if we are required to do so by law, and if we believe that such action is necessary to: (a) fulfil a government request; (b) conform with the requirements of the law or legal process; (c) protect or defend our legal rights or property, our Website, or other users; or (d) in an emergency to protect the health and safety of our Website’s users or the general public.

**Other Links / Sites**

Our Website may link to or contain links to other third party Websites that we do not control or maintain. We are not responsible for the privacy practices employed by any third party Website. We encourage you to note when you leave our Website and to read the privacy statements of all third party Websites before submitting any personally identifiable info
